export const yahoo_questions = [
    {
        "question": 'When did the first breach happen?',
        "options": ['2013', '2014', '2016'],
        "correct": '2013',
        "index": 0
    },
    {
        "question": 'When did the second breach happen',
        "options": ['2013', '2014', '2016'],
        "correct": '2014',
        "index": 1
    },
    {
        "question": 'When was the discovery',
        "options": ['2013', '2014', '2016'],
        "correct": '2016',
        "index": 2
    },
    {
        "question": 'How many users were affected in the first breach',
        "options": ['1 BIL', '200 MIL', '500 MIL'],
        "correct": '1 BIL',
        "index": 3
    },
    {
        "question": 'How many accounts were being sold?',
        "options": ['200 MIL', '500 MIL', '1 BIL'],
        "correct": '200 MIL',
        "index": 4
    },
    {
        "question": 'How many people did the FBI charge?',
        "options": ['3', '4', '5'],
        "correct": '4',
        "index": 5
    },
    {
        "question": 'How did Yahoo find out how the hackers did it',
        "options": ['Unknown', 'Spear-phishing', 'Fake cookies'],
        "correct": 'Fake cookies',
        "index": 6
    },
    {
        "question": 'The name of the seller was:',
        "options": ['Peace', 'Destruction', 'None of the above'],
        "correct": 'Peace',
        "index": 7
    },
    {
        "question": 'What did one of the buyers Peace to check for',
        "options": ['Names of 10 government officials', 'Names of 10 government eomployees', 'Names of 11 government officials'],
        "correct": 'Option 3',
        "index": 8
    },
    {
        "question": 'TRY YOUR LUCK - PICK RANDOMLY',
        "options": ['Option 1', 'Option 2', 'Option 3'],
        "correct": 'Option 2',
        "index": 9
    },
]
